#大家好 今天把兄弟的竹鼠啊 搬到那個新的廠房裡面去
Hi everyone! Today we're going to take the my buddy's bamboo rats, take them to our new site.
#現在我們那個廠房已經搞好啦
Now the new site has been furnished.
#這裡還有個花的哦
He even has a black and white one here,
#在這裡
here.
#哎呀 好重啊
Aya! It's so heavy!
#哇
Wa!
#這個最少五六十近
It's at least twenty something kilograms.
#太重啦
Too heavy
#這裡還有一個白的
Here's a white one, a white one as well.
#花的 像熊貓哦
It's black and white, like a panda.
#這麼多白的
He has so many white rats,
#有十來只誒
a dozen of them.
#你看 這裡有個花的哦
Look! Here's a black and white one.
#哇
Wa!
#公的
It's male.
#你看這個
Look at it!
#好大啊 啊
It's big, isn't it?
#它毛特別黃啊 沒洗澡
The hair is brown. I bet it has never been bathed.
#你看這個 很聽話哦
Look at it! It's nice and gentle.
#摸一下它 它很舒服
It feels very comfortable when I pet it.
#拿到我們新廠房裡面去
Take it to our new site.
#以後就是
From now on,
#我們的啦
it's ours.
#很聽話的哦 這個哦
It's really nice and gentle.
#放籠子上
Put it into the cage.
#你看 兄弟家的這隻懶貓 在這曬太陽哦
Look! This is my buddy's lazy cat. It's having a sunbath now.
#你看 兄弟家的雞
Look! My buddy's hens.
#等下我把它全部抓 通通抓走
I'll take them away, all of them.
#這是蛋雞哦 很多蛋下的
They're kept for eggs. They lay a lot of eggs.
#要分兩車裝哦 這裡 這裡只有一車 還有一車在那邊
I can't take all at a time. We'll take these here first, and then those over there.
#我等一下來裝
So these first.
#我們先把這個小的
Let's first put this small cage,
#數量少的放在下面
with fewer rats at the bottom.
#我們到了這邊咯 現在把這個竹鼠搬進去
So we're here. We'll now take the bamboo rats into the barn.
#哇
Wa!
#一車都是啊
Fully loaded.
#這個花的 哇 出來出來
This is black and white. Wa! Come out! Come out!
#這是公的哦
It's male.
#放這裡
Put it here.
#好兇啊
It's very fierce.
#哇 那麼兇 放過去吧
Wa! So fierce! Another cell.
#等它 情緒穩定之後再發
Let's wait, until, it's emotionally stable.
#給你們到新家裡面
I bring you guys to your new home,
#繁衍生息
to enjoy and to breed.
#不願意出來是不是
Don't you want to come out?
#籠子很舒服嗎
Is the cage really that comfy?
#等下直接我把你賣了
I bet you want me to sell you, now.
#這裡有一個
Here is one...
#出來
Come out!
#還是母的哦 沒懷的
It's female, not carrying...
#下次給我的那個小白
Next time my Whitey can,
#下次把那個小白拿下來
next time I'll bring Whitey here,
#給它配種
to breed with it.
#你看 就這隻 那麼兇
Look! The rat here, is really fierce.
#等它過段時間就老實了
It'll behave itself after some time.
#過段時間它就慢慢會變老實了
It'll be behaving better later.
#它肯定不知道這裡的規矩
It certainly has no ideas about the rules here.
#好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦 還有一車哦
Alright! The video ends here. We need to go back to our buddy's place,
#我們要把它 趕快把它搬過來
to take the, take the remaining rats here as soon as possible.
#要不然等下到時候兩邊跑
I don't want to go here and there.